A Guide to the Rockefeller University collection of The Medical Letter publication FA241
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller University collection of The Medical Letter publication
1959-1985
Rockefeller Archive Center
Medical Letter, Inc
FA241
302.72 Cubic Feet
688 document boxes.
Box 603
Box 604
Box 601
Box 602
Box 607
Box 608
Box 605
Box 606
Box 611
Box 612
Box 609
Box 610
Box 615
Box 616
Box 613
Box 614
Box 503
Box 504
Box 505
Box 506
Box 592
Box 591
Box 501
Box 502
Box 596
Box 595
Box 594
Box 593
Box 600
Box 599
Box 598
Box 597
Box 522
Box 521
Box 520
Box 519
Box 518
Box 517
Box 516
Box 515
Box 514
Box 513
Box 512
Box 511
Box 510
Box 509
Box 508
Box 507
Box 537
Box 538
Box 535
Box 536
Box 533
Box 534
Box 531
Box 532
Box 529
Box 530
Box 527
Box 528
Box 525
Box 526
Box 523
Box 524
Box 671
Box 672
Box 669
Box 670
Box 667
Box 668
Box 665
Box 666
Box 679
Box 680
Box 677
Box 678
Box 675
Box 676
Box 673
Box 674
Box 656
Box 655
Box 654
Box 653
Box 652
Box 651
Box 650
Box 649
Box 664
Box 663
Box 662
Box 661
Box 660
Box 659
Box 658
Box 657
Box 637
Box 638
Box 639
Box 640
Box 633
Box 634
Box 635
Box 636
Box 645
Box 646
Box 647
Box 648
Box 641
Box 642
Box 643
Box 644
Box 622
Box 621
Box 624
Box 623
Box 618
Box 617
Box 620
Box 619
Box 630
Box 629
Box 632
Box 631
Box 626
Box 625
Box 628
Box 627
Box 539
Box 540
Box 541
Box 542
Box 543
Box 544
Box 545
Box 546
Box 547
Box 548
Box 549
Box 550
Box 551
Box 552
Box 553
Box 554
Box 556
Box 555
Box 558
Box 557
Box 560
Box 559
Box 562
Box 561
Box 564
Box 563
Box 566
Box 565
Box 568
Box 567
Box 570
Box 569
Box 573
Box 574
Box 571
Box 572
Box 577
Box 578
Box 575
Box 576
Box 581
Box 582
Box 579
Box 580
Box 585
Box 586
Box 583
Box 584
Box 590
Box 589
Box 588
Box 587
Box 461
Box 460
Box 459
Box 458
Box 457
Box 456
Box 455
Box 454
Box 469
Box 468
Box 467
Box 466
Box 465
Box 464
Box 463
Box 462
Box 421
Box 422
Box 419
Box 420
Box 417
Box 418
Box 415
Box 416
Box 452
Box 453
Box 450
Box 451
Box 449
Box 449A
Box 447
Box 448
Box 491
Box 490
Box 494
Box 493
Box 487
Box 486
Box 489
Box 488
Box 683
Box 684
Box 681
Box 682
Box 687
Box 688
Box 685
Box 686
Box 474
Box 475
Box 476
Box 477
Box 470
Box 471
Box 472
Box 473
Box 482
Box 483
Box 484
Box 485
Box 478
Box 479
Box 480
Box 481
Box 498
Box 499
Box 500
Box 446
Box 495
Box 496
Box 497
Box 442
Box 443
Box 444
Box 445
Box 438
Box 439
Box 440
Box 441
Box 408
Box 409
Box 406
Box 407
Box 404
Box 405
Box 402
Box 403
Box 400
Box 401
Box 398
Box 399
Box 412
Box 411
Box 414
Box 413
Box 437
Box 436
Box 435
Box 434
Box 433
Box 432
Box 431
Box 430
Box 429
Box 428
Box 427
Box 426
Box 425
Box 424
Box 423
Box 410
Biographical/Historical note
Martin A. Rizack is an editor for THE MEDICAL LETTER. THE MEDICAL LETTER on Drugs and Therapeutics is an independent, non-profit publication providing unbiased critical evaluation of Drugs in terms of their effectiveness, adverse effects and possible alternative medications.
Scope and Contents note
Published printed material supplied by non-profit publication.
Material consists of files used in preparing articles for THE MEDICAL LETTER for the years 1959 to 1977; each file consisting of drafts of the article, letters from consultants and manufacturers; and copies of published articles from the medical and scientific literature which were used in preparing the articles. Some in folders and some in envelopes.
Additional materials are available through 1985 (Boxes 398-688) which have received standard processing, and are described in an available PDF.
Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
Materials requiring specialized equipment for access (film, audio, video, slides) may be closed to research dependent on availability of the applicable equipment
Brittle or damaged items, or materials otherwise in need of preservation care, may be closed to researchers at the discretion of the RAC Head of Archival Services/Head of Reference.
Arrangement note
Arranged chronologically.
Immediate Source of Acquisition note
Initial Date received/inventoried: July 29, 1982. Rockefeller Archive Center receives additions to the collection on an annual basis.
File Plan note
Former Classification: I 891
Conditions Governing Access note
Records are open for scholarly research twenty-five years after their creation.
Select files restricted as noted.
Pharmacology; Medicine, Preventive; Medical sciences; Medical technology; Medical research; Medical education
- "Corticosteroids-Decadron And Other Adrenal Steroids" 1:1, Issue 1, 1959 January 23 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- "Tetracyclines-Buffered Tetracyclines And Antibiotic Blood Level" 1:2. Issue 1, 1959 January 23 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- "Meprobamate-Meprobamate" 1:3, Issue 1, 1959 January 23 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- "Analgesics NIH 7519 - A New Analgesic Drug" 1:4, Issue 1, 1959 January 23 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- "Troleandomycin-Cyclamen And Tao" 1:5, Issue 2, 1959 February 6 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- "Iproniazid Marsilid" 1:6, Issue 2, 1959 February 6 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- "Lipids-Dietary Aids For Reducing Blood Cholestrol" 1:8, Issue 2, 1959 February 6 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- "Thyroid (Hormones) - Cytomel And Trionine" 1:9, Issue 3, 1959 February 20; 1 of 2 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- "Thyroid (Hormones) - Cytomel And Trionine" 1:9, Issue 3, 1959 February 20; 2 of 2 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- "Thyroid (Hormones) - The Choice And Cost Of Thyroid Preparations" 1:10, Issue 3, 1959 February 20 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- "Thyroid Function Tests" 1:11, Issue 3, 1959 February 20 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- "Antihistamines-Dimetane" 1:14, Issue 4, 1959 March 6 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- "Tetracycline-Tetracyclines And Nystatin", 1:15, Issue 4, 1959 March 6 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- "Zoxyzolamine", 1:16, Issue 4, 1959 March 6 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- "Diabinese Correspondence" Issue 4, 1959 March 6 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- "Diabetes, Therapy-Orinase And Diabetes" 1:17, Issue 5, 1959 March 20 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- "Erythromycin Esolate Ilosine" 1:18, Issue 5, 1959 March 20 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- "Phenothiazines (Trimeprazine) Temaril" 1:19, Issue 5, 1959 March 20 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- "Corticosteroids (Dexamethasone) - Follow Up Deramethasone" 1:20, Issue 5, 1959 March 20 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- "Chloramphenicol-Chloromycetin" 1:2, Issue 6, 1959 April 3 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- "Anileridine Leritine" 1:22, Issue 6, 1959 April 3 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- "Ethoheptazine-Zactane And Zactirin" 1:23, Issue 6, 1959 April 3 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- "Syrosingopine-Singoserp" 1:25, Issue 7, 1959 April 17 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- "Senna-Senokot" 1:26, Issue 7, 1959 April 17 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- "Eye Disease-Opthalmic Steroid Preparations And Mixtures" 1:27, April 17, Issue 7, 1959 April 17 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- "Phenylbutazone-Butazolidin And Sterazolidin" 1:30, Issue 8, 1959 May 1 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- "Amphotericin B-Fungizone" 1:32, Issue 8, 1959 May 1 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- "Streptococcal Infections-Drug Cost In Control Of Streptococcus Infections" 1:34, Issue 9, 1959 May 15; 1 of 2 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- "Streptococcal Infections-Drug Cost In Control Of Streptococcus Infections" 1:34, Issue 9, 1959 May 15; 2 of 2 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- "Nitrofurantoin-Furadantin" 1:37, Issue 10, 1959 May 29 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- "Fuzazolidone-Furoxone" 1:38, Issue 10, 1959 May 29; 1 of 2 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- "Fuzazolidone-Furoxone" 1:38, Issue 10, 1959 May 29; 2 of 2 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- "Dextropropoxyphene-Darvon" 1:40, Issue 10, 1959 May 29 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- "Syrosingopine-Notes On Singoserp" 1:40, Issue 10, 1959 May 29 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- "Antimicrobials-Spontin And Vancocini" 1:41. Issue 11, 1959 June 12 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- "Poison Ivy-Prophylaxis Of Poison Ivy Dermatitis" 1:42, Issue 11, 1959 June 12 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- "Syrosingopine-More On Singoserp" 1:44, Issue 11, 1959 June 12 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- "Nutrition And Diet-Sustagen" 1:47. Issue 12, 1959 June 26 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- "Antihistamines-Non-Prescription Sleep Aids", 1:48, Issue 12, 1959 June 26 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- "Psoralens-Methoxysalen For Vitiligo And Suntanning" 1:49, Issue 13, 1959 July 10 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- "Penicillin-Penicillin V Versus Penicillin G, 1:50, Issue 13, 1959 July 10 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- "Griseofulvin" 1:51, Issue 13, 1959 July 10 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- "Psoriasis-Alphosyl" 1:51, Issue 13, 1959 July 10 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- "Nutrition And Diet (Sustagen) - Sustagen A Correction" 1:52, Issue 13, 1959 July 10 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- "Mecamylamine-Inversine" 1:53, Issue 14, 1959 July 24 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- "Heparin-Clarin" 1:54, Issue 14, 1959 July 24; 1 of 2 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- "Heparin-Clarin" 1:54, Issue 14, 1959 July 24; 2 of 2 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- "Iron-Oral Iron Preparations", 1:55, Issue 14, 1959 July 24; 1 of 2 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- "Iron-Oral Iron Preparations", 1:55, Issue 14, 1959 July 24; 2 of 2 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- "Phenothiazines-Prochlorperazine Compazine" 1:57, Issue 15, 1959 August 7; 1 of 2 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- "Phenothiazines-Prochlorperazine Compazine" 1:57, Issue 15, 1959 August 7; 2 of 2 (Box 4, Folder 12)
- "Newborn-Drug Hazards In The Newborn" 1:58, Issue 15, 1959 August 7 (Box 4, Folder 13)
- "Parkinson's Disease-Antiparkinsonism Drug", 1:59, Issue 15, 1959 August 7; 1 of 2 (Box 4, Folder 14)
- "Parkinson's Disease-Antiparkinsonism Drug", 1:59, Issue 15, 1959 August 7; 2 of 2 (Box 4, Folder 15)
- "Griseofulvin" 1:61, Issue 16, 1959 August 21 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- "Bretylium Tosylate-A New Antihypersensitive Drug" 1:64, Issue 16, 1959 August 12 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- "Imipramine-Tofranil" 1:65, Issue 17, 1959 September 4; 1 of 2 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- "Imipramine-Tofranil" 1:65, Issue 17, 1959 September 4; 2 of 2 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- "Vitamins-B12" 1:67, Issue 17, 1959 September 4 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- "Anergex" 1:68, Issue 17, 1959 September 4 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- "Rauwolfias-Rauwolfias Products In Hypertension" 1:70, Issue 18, 1959 September 18; 1 of 2 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- "Rauwolfias-Rauwolfias Products In Hypertension" 1:70, Issue 18, 1959 September 18; 2 of 2 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- "Diagnostic Tests (Glucose) - Enzyme Tests For Urine Sugar" 1:72, Issue 18, 1959 September 18 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- "Sulfonamides-Long Acting Sulfonamides" 1:73, Issue 19, 1959 October 2; 1 of 2 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- "Sulfonamides-Long Acting Sulfonamides" 1:73, Issue 19, 1959 October 2; 2 of 2 (Box 5, Folder 11)
- "Furaltadone-Altafur" 1:75, Issue 19, 1959 October 2 (Box 5, Folder 12)
- "Skin Disease Therapy-Acid Mantle Creme" 1:76, Issue 19, 1959 October 2 (Box 5, Folder 13)
- "Depression Therapy-A Note On Drug Therapy Of Depression" 1:77, Issue 20, 1959 October 16 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- "Isocarboxazid-Marplan" 1:78, Issue 20, 1959 October 16; 1 of 2 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- "Isocarboxazid-Marplan" 1:78, Issue 20, 1959 October 16; 2 of 2 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- "Costicosteroids-Note On Adrenal Steroids" 1:80, Issue 20, 1959 October 16 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- "Antihistamines-Palaramine And Disomer" 1:83, Issue 21, 1959 October 30; 1 of 2 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- "Antihistamines-Palarmine And Disomer" 1:83, Issue 21, 1959 October 30; 2 of 2 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- "Antimicrobials-Dihydrostrptomycin And Kanamycin" 1:83, Issue 21, 1959 October 30 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- "Anticoagulants-Oral Anticoagulant Drugs" 1:85, Issue 22, 1959 November 13; 1 of 4 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- "Anticoagulants-Oral Anticoagulant Drugs" 1:85, Issue 22, 1959 November 13; 2 of 4 (Box 6, Folder 9)
- "Anticoagulants-Oral Anticoagulant Drugs" 1:85, Issue 22, 1959 November 13; 3 of 4 (Box 6, Folder 10)
- "Anticoagulants-Oral Anticoagulant Drugs" 1:85, Issue 22, 1959 November 13; 4 of 4 (Box 6, Folder 11)
- "Penicillin Allergy-Penicillin" 1:87, Issue 22, 1959 November 13; 1 of 2 (Box 6, Folder 12)
- "Penicillin Allergy-Penicillin" 1:87, Issue 22, 1959 November 13; 2 of 2 (Box 6, Folder 13)
- "Respiratory Disease (Vaccines) - Vaccines For Respiratory Virus Infection" 1:88, Issue 22, 1959 November 13 (Box 6, Folder 14)
- "Tetracyclines-Declomycin" 1:89, Issue 23, 1959 November 27; 1 of 2 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- "Tetracyclines-Declomycin" 1:89, Issue 23, 1959 November 27; 2 of 2 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- "Hypertension-Pitfalls In Some Life Insurance Statistics" 1:90, Issue 23, 1959 November 27 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- "Meprobate Prepns-Deprol" 1:92, Issue 23, 1959 November 27 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- "Fibrinolytic Agents-Actase And Streptokinase", 1:93, Issue 24, 1959 December 11; 1 of 2 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- "Fibrinolytic Agents-Actase And Streptokinase", 1:93, Issue 24, 1959 December 11; 2 of 2 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- "Corticosteroids, Topical-Topical Corticosteroids" 1:94, Issue 24, 1959 December 11; 1 of 2 (Box 7, Folder 7)
- "Corticosteroids, Tropical-Tropical Corticosteroids" 1:94, Issue 24, 1959 December 11; 2 of 2 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- "Immunization (Vaccines) Quadrigan And Tetravex" 1:96, Issue 24, 1959 December 11 (Box 7, Folder 9)
- "Penicillins-Syncillin", 1:97, Issue 25, 1959 December 25 (Box 7, Folder 10)
- "Liver Diseases-Infections Hepatitis And Immune Globulin" 1:98, Issue 25, 1959 December 25 (Box 7, Folder 11)
- "Epilepsy-Anti-Epilepsy Drug" 1:99, Issue 25, 1959 December 25; 1 of 3 (Box 7, Folder 12)
- "Epilepsy-Anti-Epilepsy Drug" 1:99, Issue 25, 1959 December 25; 2 of 3 (Box 7, Folder 13)
- "Epilepsy-Anti-Epilepsy Drug" 1:99, Issue 25, 1959 December 25; 3 of 3 (Box 7, Folder 14)
- "Smoking-Smoking And Lung Cancer" 2:1, Issue 26, 1960 January 8 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- "Iron, Injectable-Imferon" 2:2, Issue 26, 1960 January 8; 1 of 2 (Box 8, Folder 2)
- "Iron, Injectable-Imferon" 2:2, Issue 26, 1960 January 8; 2 of 2 (Box 8, Folder 3)
- "Parasitic Infections-Povan And Other Anthelmintic Drugs" 2:4, Issue 26, 1960 January 8 (Box 8, Folder 4)
- "Chloroquines-Manuscript Aralen And Plaquenil" 2:5, Issue 27, 1960 January 22; 1 of 2 (Box 8, Folder 5)
- "Chloroquines-Manuscript Aralen And Plaquenil" 2:5, Issue 27, 1960 January 22; 2 of 2 (Box 8, Folder 6)
- "Progestational Hormones-Enovid, Norlutin And Delalutin" 2:7, Issue 27, 1960 January 22; 1 of 3 (Box 8, Folder 7)
- "Progestational Hormones-Enovid, Norlutin, and Delalutin" 2:7, Issue 27, 1960 January 22; 2 of 3 (Box 8, Folder 8)
- "Progestational Hormones-Enovid, Norlutin, and Delalutin" 2:7, Issue 27, 1960 January 22; 3 of 3 (Box 8, Folder 9)
- "Hydroxyzine-Atarax And Vistril" 2:9, Issue 28, 1960 February 5; 1 of 4 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- "Hydroxyzine-Atarax And Vistril" 2:9, Issue 28, 1960 February 5; 2 of 4 (Box 9, Folder 2)
- "Hydroxyzine-Atarax And Vistril" 2:9, Issue 28, 1960 February 5; 3 of 4 (Box 9, Folder 3)
- "Hydroxyzine-Atarax And Vistril" 2:9, Issue 28, 1960 February 5; 4 of 4 (Box 9, Folder 4)
- "Obesity-Appetite Depressants" 2:11, Issue 28, 1960 February 5 (Box 9, Folder 5)
- "Corticosteroids, Topical-Topical Corticosteroids - A Correction", 2:12, Issue 28, 1960 February 5 (Box 9, Folder 6)
- "Trimethidinium Methosulfate Otensin - A New Antihypertensive" 2:13, Issue 29, 1960 February 19; 1 of 2 (Box 9, Folder 7)
- "Trimethidinium Methosulfate Otensin - A New Antihypertensive" 2:13, Issue 29, 1960 February 19; 2 of 2 (Box 9, Folder 8)
- "Tetracyclines, Syntetrin - A New Parenteral Tetracycline" 2:14, Issue 29, 1960 February 19 (Box 9, Folder 9)
- "Angina Pectoris-Organic Nitrates For The Control Of Angina Pectoris" 2:17, Issue 30, 1960 March 14; 1 Of 3 (Box 10, Folder 1)
- "Angina Pectoris-Organic Nitrates For The Control Of Angina Pectoris" 2:17, Issue 30, 1960 March 14; 2 Of 3 (Box 10, Folder 2)
- "Angina Pectoris-Organic Nitrates For The Control Of Angina Pectoris" 2:17, Issue 30, 1960 March 14; 3 of 3 (Box 10, Folder 3)
- "Flavonoids-CVP" 2:19, Issue 30, 1960 March 4 (Box 10, Folder 4)
- "Parasitic Infections-Pinworms" 2:20, Issue 30, 1960 March 4 (Box 10, Folder 5)
- "Cyclophosphamide-Cytoxan" 2:21, Issue 31, 1960 March 18; 1 of 2 (Box 10, Folder 6)
- "Cyclophosphamide-Cytoxan" 2:21, Issue 31, 1960 March 18; 2 of 2 (Box 10, Folder 7)
- "Shock Therapy-Vasopressor Drugs For Shock" 2:22, Issue 31, 1960 March 18; 1 of 2 (Box 10, Folder 8)
- "Shock Therapy-Vasopressor Drugs For Shock" 2:22, Issue 31, 1960 March 18; 2 of 2 (Box 10, Folder 9)
- "Salicylates-Arthropan" 2:23, Issue 31, 1960 March 18; 1 of 2 (Box 10, Folder 10)
- "Salicylates-Arthropan" 2:23, Issue 31, 1960 March 18; 2 of 2 (Box 10, Folder 11)
- "Estrogen-Premarin for Bleeding" 2:28, Issue 32, 1960 April 1 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- "Shock Therapy-Levophed and Aramine" 2:29, Issue 33, 1960 April 15; 1 of 2 (Box 11, Folder 2)
- "Estrogen-Premarin for Bleeding" 2:28, Issue 32, 1960 April 1 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- "Shock Therapy-Levophed and Aramine" 2:29, Issue 33, 1960 April 15; 1 of 2 (Box 11, Folder 2)
- "Shock Therapy-Levophed and Aramine" 2:29, Issue 33, 1960 April 15; 2 of 2 (Box 11, Folder 3)
- "Phemetrazine-Preludin" 2:31, Issue 33, 1960 April 15; 1 of 2 (Box 11, Folder 4)
- "Phemetrazine-Preludin" 2:31, Issue 33, 1960 April 15; 2 of 2 (Box 11, Folder 5)
- "Vitamins-Homagenets and Vitamin Absorption" 2:32, Issue 33, 1960 April 15; 1 of 2 (Box 11, Folder 6)
- "Vitamins-Homagenets and Vitamin Absorption: 2:32, Issue 33, 1960 April 15; 2 of 2 (Box 11, Folder 7)
- "Methyprylon-Noludar, A "Non-Barbiturate" Hypnotic" 2:35, Issue 34, 1960 April 29; 1 of 2 (Box 11, Folder 8)
- "Methyprylon-Noludar, A "Non-Barbiturate" Hypnotic" 2:35, Issue 34, 1960 April 29; 2 of 2 (Box 11, Folder 9)
- "Halothane-Fluothane" 2:36, Issue 34, 1960 April 29 (Box 11, Folder 10)
- "Polyurethane Foam-Ostamer" 2:36, Issue 34, 1960 April 29 (Box 11, Folder 11)
- "Chlordiazepoxide-Librium" 2:37, Issue 35, 1960 May 13; 1 of 2 (Box 12, Folder 1)
- "Chlordiazepoxide-Librium" 2:37, Issue 35, 1960 May 13; 2 of 2 (Box 12, Folder 2)
- "Diarrhea-Traveler's Diarrhea" 2:38, Issue 35, 1960 May 13 (Box 12, Folder 3)
- "Iron, Injectable-Imteron" 2:40, Issue 35, 1960 May 13 (Box 12, Folder 4)
- "Estrogens-Estrogens for Menopausal Symptoms" 2:41, Issue 36, 1960 May 27; 1 of 2 (Box 12, Folder 5)
- "Estrogens-Estrogens for Menopausal Symptoms" 2:41, Issue 36, 1960 May 27; 2 of 2 (Box 12, Folder 6)
- "Analgesics (Antipyretic) Pabalate" 2:43, Issue 36, 1960 May 27 (Box 12, Folder 7)
- "Contraceptives-The Birth Control Pill" 2:45, Issue 37, 1960 June 10 (Box 12, Folder 8)
- "Progestational Hormones-Provera" 2:46, Issue 37, 1960 June 10 (Box 12, Folder 9)
- "Antimicrobials-Hot Weather Stability of Antibotics" 2:48, Issue 37, 1960 June 10 (Box 12, Folder 10)
- "Shock Therapy-Five Vasporessors" 2:50, Issue 38, 1960 June 24 (Box 13, Folder 1)
- "Nutrition & Diet-Metrecal" 2:51, Issue 38, 1960 June 24 (Box 13, Folder 2)
- "Ergotamine Prepns-New and Old Ergotamine Drugs for Migraine" 2:54, Issue 39, 1960 July 8; 1 of 2 (Box 13, Folder 3)
- "Ergotamine Prepns-New and Old Ergotamine Drugs for Migraine" 2:54, Issue 39, 1960 July 8; 2 of 2 (Box 13, Folder 4)
- "Corticotropin-ACTH Versus Corticosteroids" 2:55, Issue 39, 1960 July 8 (Box 13, Folder 5)
- "Anisindione-Miradon, A New Anticoagulant" 2:58, Issue 40, 1960 July 22 (Box 13, Folder 6)
- "Nitrofurans-Reappraisal of Three Oval Nitrofurans" 2:62, Issue 41, 1960 August 5; 1 of 2 (Box 13, Folder 7)
- "Nitrofurans-Reappraisal of Three Oval Nitrofurans" 2:62, Issue 41, 1960 August 5; 2 of 2 (Box 13, Folder 8)
- "Skin Disease (Diaper Rash) Prevention of Diaper Rash" 2:64, Issue 41, 1960 August 5 (Box 13, Folder 9)
- "Corticosteroids (Prednisone) - Tests of Prednisone" 2:65, Issue 42, 1960 August 19; 1 of 2 (Box 14, Folder 1)
- "Corticisteroids (Prednisone) - Tests of Prednisone" 2:65, Issue 42, 1960 August 19; 2 of 2 (Box 14, Folder 2)
- "Hypnotics & Sedatives-Dorraison, Placidyl, and Valmid" 2:67, Issue 42, 1960 August 19; 1 of 2 (Box 14, Folder 3)
- "Hypnotics & Sedatives-Dorraison, Placidyl, and Valmid" 2:67, Issue 42, 1960 August 19; 2 of 2 (Box 14, Folder 4)
- "Furaltadine-Further Note on Altafur" 2:68, Issue 42, 1960 August 19 (Box 14, Folder 5)
- "Guadethidine-Ismelin" 2:69, Issue 43, 1960 September 2; 1 of 2 (Box 14, Folder 6)
- "Guadethidine-Ismelin" 2:69, Issue 43, 1960 September 2; 2 of 2 (Box 14, Folder 7)
- "Polio Vaccines-Oral Polio Vaccines" 2:71, Issue 43, 1960 September 2 (Box 14, Folder 8)
- "Polio Vaccines-Purivax" 2:72; Issue 43, 1960 September 2 (Box 14, Folder 9)
- "Urinanalysis-Ketostix and Actest Tablets" 2:72, Issue 45, 1960 September 2 (Box 14, Folder 10)
- "Penicillins-Phenthicillin" 2:73, Issue 44, 1960 September 16; 1 of 2 (Box 15, Folder 1)
- "Penicillins-Phenthicillin" 2:73, Issue 44, 1960 September 16; 2 of 2 (Box 15, Folder 2)
- "Penicillins, New (Methicillin) - A New Penicillin for Resistant Staphylococci" 2:75, Issue 44, 1960 September 16; 1 of 2 (Box 15, Folder 3)
- "Penicillins, New (Methicillin) - A New Penicillin for Resistant Staphylococci" 2:75, Issue 44, 1960 September 16; 2 of 2 (Box 15, Folder 4)
- "Phenothiazines (Fluphenazine) - Prolixln and Permitil" 2:77, Issue 45, 1960 September 30; 1 of 2 (Box 15, Folder 5)
- "Phenothiazines (Fluphenazine) - Prolixin and Permitil" 2:77, Issue 45, 1960 September 30; 2 of 2 (Box 15, Folder 6)
- "Anticoagulants-Anticoagulant Drugs and Surgery" 2:78, Issue 45, 1960 September 30 (Box 15, Folder 7)
- "Urinanalysis-Albustix" 2:79, Issue 45, 1960 September 30 (Box 15, Folder 8)
- "Triparanol-Mer/29" 2:81, Issue 46, 1960 October 14 (Box 16, Folder 1)
- "Skin Disease, Therapy-Acne Cleansers" 2:83, Issue 46, 1960 October 14 (Box 16, Folder 2)
- "Oxymorphone-Numorphan" 2:85, Issue 47, 1960 October 28; 1 of 2 (Box 16, Folder 3)
- "Oxymorphone-Numorphan" 2:85, Issue 47, 1960 October 28; 2 of 2 (Box 16, Folder 4)
- "Corticosteroids, Topical-Diloderm" 2:86, Issue 47, 1960 October 28 (Box 16, Folder 5)
- "Meprobamate" 2:87, Issue 47, 1960 October 28; 1 of 2 (Box 16, Folder 6)
- "Meprobamate" 2:87, Issue 47, 1960 October 28; 2 of 2 (Box 16, Folder 7)
- "Respiratory Disease (Vaccines) - Resprogen and Influenza Vaccines" 2:89, Issue 48, 1960 November 11 (Box 17, Folder 1)
- "Thyroid Disease (Hyperthyroidism) - Drug Treatment of Hyperthyroidism" 2:90, Issue 48, 1960 November 11; 1 of 2 (Box 17, Folder 2)
- "Thyroid Disease (Hyperthyroidism) - Drug Treatment of Hyperthyroisism" 2:90, Issue 48, 1960 November 11; 2 of 2 (Box 17, Folder 3)
- "Vitamins, Niacin-Nicalex" 2:91, Issue 48, 1960 November 11 (Box 17, Folder 4)
- "Methenamine-Mandelamine, and Urinary Tract Infections" 2:93, Issue 49, 1960 November 25; 1 of 2 (Box 17, Folder 5)
- "Methenamine-Mandelamine, and Urinary Tract Infections" 2:93, Issue 49, 1960 November 25; 2 of 2 (Box 17, Folder 6)
- "Antacids-Antacids in Ulcer Therapy" 2:94, Issue 49, 1960 November 25; 1 of 3 (Box 17, Folder 7)
- "Antacids-Anactids in Ulcer Therapy" 2:94, Issue 49, 1960 November 25; 2 of 3 (Box 17, Folder 8)
- "Antacids-Anactids in Ulcer Therapy" 2:94, Issue 49, 1960 November 25; 3 of 3 (Box 17, Folder 9)
- "Nasal Decongestants-Otrivin" 2:96, Issue 49, 1960 November 25 (Box 17, Folder 10)
- "Phenazocine-Prinadol" 2:97, Issue 50, 1960 December 9; 1 of 2 (Box 18, Folder 1)
- "Phenazocine-Prinadol" 2:97, Issue 50, 1960 December 9; 2 of 2 (Box 18, Folder 2)
- "Vitamins-Multi Vitamin Supplements" 2:98, Issue 50, 1960 December 9 (Box 18, Folder 3)
- "Corticosteroids, Side Effects-Corticosteriod Therapy in Children" 2:99, Issue 50, 1960 December 9; 1 of 2 (Box 18, Folder 4)
- "Costicosteroids, Side Effects-Corticosteriod Therapy in Children" 2:99, Issue 50, 1960 December 9; 2 of 2 (Box 18, Folder 5)
- "Meprobamate-Mephobamate Toxicity" 2:100, Issue 50, 1960 December 9 (Box 18, Folder 6)
- "Oxethazine-Oxaine" 2:103, Issue 51, 1960 December 23 (Box 18, Folder 7)
- "Chloral Hydrate" 2:104, Issue 51, 1960 December 23 (Box 18, Folder 8)
- "Chloramphenicol-Chloromycetin and Aplastic Anemia" 3:1, Issue 52, 1961 January 6 (Box 19, Folder 1)
- "Antimicrobials, Prophylactic Use (Respiratory Disease) - Antibiotic Prophylaxis of Chronic Bronchitis" 3:2, Issue 52, 1961 January 6 (Box 19, Folder 2)
- "Amphemdone-Dornwal" 3:4, Issue 52, 1961 January 6; 1 of 3 (Box 19, Folder 3)
- "Amphemdone-Dornwal" 3:4, Issue 52, 1961 January 6; 2 of 3 (Box 19, Folder 4)
- "Amphemdone-Dornwal" 3:4, Issue 52, 1961 January 6; 3 of 3 (Box 19, Folder 5)